<Document>
  # Traitors

  <Box>
    [color=#999999][italic]"WHISKEY. ECHO. WHISKEY. LIMA. ALPHA. DELTA. AGENT, YOU HAVE BEEN ACTIVATED."[/italic][/color]
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PosterContrabandSyndicateRecruitment" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  Traitors are antagonists employed by the [color=#ff0000]Syndicate.[/color]

  Unlike other servers, Traitors on Ephemeral Space are a team antagonist--closer to a mix of Traitors and Nuclear Operatives.

  Traitors have three phases of objectives: completing their basic objectives, hacking the nuclear cryptographic terminals, and then detonating the nuke.
  Each phase of objectives must be completed before the next can be attempted: the terminals can't be hacked without the basic objectives done, and the nuke can't be detonated if the terminals aren't hacked.

  Basic objectives include things like killing specific targets and sabotaging certain machines around the station.

  Hacking the terminals is done simply by opening their UI and clicking the button. Terminals show you the location of the disk as a blinking white dot, and anyone who checks them can see that they're hacked after it's done.
  The terminals are located in [bold]the HoS's office, the captain's office, and secure tech storage.[/bold]

  The nuke can be disarmed--but the detonation timer is significantly shorter than normal, at only 60 seconds. If you fail at that point, it's your own fault.

  The basic objectives, of which you get three, include:
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorKillRandom"/>
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorSabotageCommunications"/>
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorSabotageCrewMonitoring"/>
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorSabotageIDComputer"/>
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorSabotageCriminalRecords"/>
  <ESGBObjectiveEmbed Objective="ESObjectiveTraitorSabotageTelecom"/>
  [color=red]TODO ES write the rest lol[/color]

  [color=red]TODO ES write mask entries[/color]
</Document>
